Christmas with the Darlings is a romance, tv movie
film directed by Catherine Cyran.
Just before the holidays Jessica Lew is ending her tenure as the assistant to her wealthy boss to use her recently earned law degree within
his company, but offers to help his charming, younger brother as he looks after his orphaned nieces and nephew over Christmas.
Jessica Lew, played by Katrina Law.
Max Darlington, played by Carlo Marks.
Charles Darlington, played by Steve Bacic.
Emma Darlington, played by Islie Hirvonen.
J Henry Darlington, played by Anthony Bolognese.
Abby Darlington, played by Madeline Hirvonen.
Dane William DeHaan ( də-HAHN; born 1985 or 1986) is an American actor.
His roles include Andrew Detmer in Chronicle (2012), Jason Glanton in The Place Beyond the Pines (2012), Lucien Carr in Kill Your Darlings (2013), Harry Osborn / Green Goblin in The Amazing Spider-Man 2
(2014), Lockhart in A Cure for Wellness (2016), Valerian in Valerian and the City of a Thousand Planets (2017), Chris Lynwood in ZeroZeroZero, and Kenneth Nichols in Oppenheimer (2023).
In 2021, he starred in the psychological romance
horror miniseries Lisey's Story.
He also had a role in the true crime limited series
adaptation of The Staircase in 2022.
The tone is emotional.